Sorry , this is all that he knows .
Do you live alone in Kolkata ?
Yes .
Don 't you get bored ?
No .
Then why do you want to get married ?
Actually , I didn 't have any plans of getting married .
Do you want to ask me anything ?
You ...
You 're studying to be a nurse , right ?
I have finished my course . Doing my internship now .
Can I ask you something ?
Yes .
Have you ever had an affair ?
No .
Never ?
No , I 've never had an affair .
I had a boyfriend .
He was a doctor , but we broke up .
Actually , now that I think of it , I liked his bike more than him .
You know ... it was so cool .
Do you ride a bike ?
I have tried a couple of times .
But I get very nervous .
You should try doing yoga . It will really calm you down .
Yoga ?
We were taught yoga to calm patients down before an operation .
Keep your finger on your nose and ...
Take a deep breath .
Try it .
What , now ?
Keep your finger on your nose and ...
Take a deep breath .
Breathe out .
Now breathe in from the other side .
Should I remove this finger ?
Breathe in from the other side .
There , it has started raining again .
Babai , how did you like her ?
She was okay .
What do you mean she was okay ?
Did you like her or not ?
I did .
So Babai , should we go ahead ?
No , let us wait for their response .
Oh ho , you don 't need to worry about that .
I know for sure that they will say yes .
How do you know that ? Huh ?
Whatever the outcome , this is the last try , okay ?
Look , you are overreacting now .
Ask your mother , I found her after seventeen rejections .
All this is destiny .
Are you okay ?
Babai , no ! Babai !
Mother , sit inside the car .
We were returning from Barrackpore .
It was raining heavily .
Suddenly , she jumped in front of our car .
Jumped in front ?
What do you mean ? Suicide ?
Yes .
Do you remember where the accident took place ?
An old woman met with an accident here , a few hours ago .
She was wearing a burkha .
Has anybody seen anything ?
No .
Does anyone know who she was ?
There are a lot of Muslims who stay nearby .
How will we know who it is under the burkha ?
This belongs to the dog lady .
Who ?
I don 't know her name . But everyone calls her the dog lady .
Where does she live ?
At the end of the lane you see in front , there is a pond ...
After which , there is a jungle .
She has a little hut there .
Sir , can I say something ?
That woman was weird and crazy .
She wouldn 't talk to anyone .
She would pick up stray dogs and take them home .
This is why everybody called her the dog lady .
Look around if you find anyone .
Okay , sir .
She would roam the streets at night .
Sit alone and cry loudly .
We could hear screams coming from her hut sometimes .
Is anyone there ?
No sir . There 's no one there .
Mother ...
Don 't be scared , I 'm a police officer .
I have come here to help you .
Yes !
Should I remove this ?
Mother will come and take it off .
Your mother has met with an accident .
You need to go to the hospital .
Go to sleep ...
She came in front of our car all of a sudden .
- We were taking her to the hospital ... - You , sign here !
Sign .
Is there anyone else at home ?
Any relative ...
Collect the body from the police morgue tomorrow .
You have to pay three hundred rupees for the discharge .
- You have to pay it now . - Yes , I will give it to you .
Take this .
What will they do to my mother ?
Nothing much . They need to investigate .
How will you go to the morgue ?
Do you want me to take you ?
I will take you there .
Why do you need to go there ?
That poor girl has no one . Somebody should accompany her .
So ? What is it to us ?
Why are you getting involved , unnecessarily ?
Unnecessarily ?
Mother , I was sitting in the front . I know ...
it was not a case of suicide .
- What happened ? - You have to go to the police station .
There 's no problem as such .
From what the villagers said ...
The police think that it was a case of suicide .
But that girl ? Will she create any problems ?
No madam ! She doesn 't even know who her father is .
Don 't you know ?
Her mother had kept her shackled , like an animal .
Look at what 's going on nowadays .
Everybody is scared of getting robbed . Nobody wears gold anymore .
What happened ? Did you find anything ?
Where are you going ? The doctor will be here soon .
- Hello ! - Sir ..
There 's a body here .
She died in an accident . A Muslim woman .
- Do you want me to come for the funeral ? - No , she has that sign on her arm .
Sign ?
Of the Oladhchakra .
Now it is time for you to start eating by yourself .
Do you understand ?
Open . Here .
Chew it nicely .
There is an article in the Bangladesh Tribune .
Have you read it ?
Did you note down the point on Hussain Saab ?
Bangladesh Tribune !
Yes , I have , sir .
Near Satkhira ...
they have found some skulls , of children .
So , this is nothing new . It has happened before .
These bodies from the Liberation War ...
God knows how many more are there .
Yes , but according to the report they are not from the Liberation War ...
they are from the Doomsday Movement .
Is it ?
Sir , may I ask you something ?
Have you ever seen a Djinn ?
No .
Grandpa , what is a Djinn ?
What is a Djinn ?
Explain it to him .
The naughty thoughts that you have ...
Like , " I don 't want to go to school ! "
" I won 't go to bed early ! "
" I will disturb you when you are working ! "
" I will talk about useless things . "
Huh ...
This is the work of a Djinn ...
What we call the devil .
- They are very dangerous . Eat this . - More dangerous than Ifrit ?
Eat yourself .
Greetings , Faris .
Alright , I 'll be there .
' Near Satkhira ... ' ' They have found some skulls , of children . '
' According to the report , they are from the Doomsday Movement . '
That 's it ... It 's almost over .
No ... no ... no .
Don 't be scared . It 's only for a little while .
Bear the pain . It will be over soon .
Faris , how many are left ?
Twelve .
Calm down , it will be alright .
Where do you live ?
Huh ?
Who else is there at home ?
Keep that back .
What are you doing ? You will get hurt .
Keep it back , you will get hurt .
Did you hear me ?
Give it to me . Give it back to me , now !
Faris !
What happened , professor ? Where 's that girl ?
Find her !
Sharib , Shamsher , Rafiq ! Let 's go .
Keep a look out , my house will be on the right .
Rubina Khatun ?
Come here and sign .
Just a minute .
Is she the daughter ?
Yes .
Does she have any more daughters ? Or just one ?
What is it to you ?
I was just asking .
Oh madam , carry on !
She has been given a bath , come inside .
Please move aside .
Why is she lighting that ?
What ?
Those ... those sticks .
Those foul smelling sticks .
But those are incense sticks . They smell good .
No , no . Stop them .
- Stop them now . I don 't like it . - Alright then ... I will tell them .
Listen ... that 's enough . Thank you . That 's enough .
You leave .
I 'll go by myself .
Sure ?
Just a minute .
Can you hold this , please ?
Keep this with you .
Just take it , you will need it .
Alright then , I will leave .
Which way is the pond ?
Okay , I can find my way from here .
Keep this with you . You will need it now .
Bye .
Rukku ...
Come here ... to me .
Who are you ?
Mother ?
Rukhsana ...
My child ...
Come here .
Rukhsana ...
Come here , my child .
Rukku ...
Come here .
He is coming to ask you for something .
You 'll have to give it .
Is it working alright now ? I hope nothing has been left out .
Hello ?
Hi , are you busy ?
Oh , it 's you . No , tell me .
My mother would have called ...
But I thought of telling you first . I have agreed to the marriage .
Oh okay . I mean ...
Actually , I wanted to tell you something else as well .
Can we meet today ?
My shift gets over at four o 'clock .
Earlier , I would come here every year .
For the book fair .
It used to be so lovely here .
I don 't know why they shifted it .
You wanted to tell me something ?
Er ...
That man I told you about ...
The doctor with the bike ?
Yes , him . The doctor with the bike .
Our affair ...
Didn 't end just like that .
We were serious about each other .
It lasted for four years . And then ...
And then ?
It just ended one day .
Now ...
that you know about this ,
will you refuse to marry me ?
Actually , I have told my parents ...
No ... no ...
This is where she lives .
You go ahead , professor . I will take care of it .
He will kill me ...
Please , save me .
Save me .
Take this .
Drink it .
Come on .
It is hot .
Blow on it .
Now tell me ...
Who wants to kill you ?
That ... that man .
Who had got those foul smelling sticks .
Who is that man ? Do you know him ?
I had seen him when I was a little girl .
Where ?
In the mountains ...
Mother and I used to live in the mountains .
He had come .
Mother untied me and told me to run away .
Run , Ruku !
He was following us .
I ran and ran .
I was tired ... but I kept on running .
We managed to escape .
Why did he want to kill you ?
I don 't know . Mother never told me .
Do you know his name ?
How did you manage to come here ?
I mean ...
Did you walk all the way ?
I ran .
Sorry . Take this medicine .
Why don 't you apply it on your feet ?
Do you want me to hold your glass ?
Press the tube .
When did you wake up ?
Do you want some tea ?
So tell me , do you want to go to the police ?
No .
The police must have informed him .
How do you know that ?
The police knows where I live .
So do I.
Does that mean I 've informed them ?
Where will you go now ?
Do you have any relatives ?
Any place to go to ?
Alright then ...
You can stay here . I will figure something out .
I am getting late for work .
You know what ...
I will keep your food on the table .
Make sure you eat it .
Is it alright if I lock the door from outside ?
How will I cut my nails ?
Huh ?
Nails ...
Hey , you fool !
- How are you , Faris ? - I am good , sir .
Have you spoken with Mr. Aalam ?
Yes .
He said it will take a couple of days .
She is spotted now and then .
But it is difficult to bring her under control .
Tell me something Faris ...
I hope we are not doing something wrong .
What are you talking about , professor ?
This is the third time that girl has escaped .
Before we started the revolution , professor ...
You had said ...
To stop doomsday ,
To stop Ifrit ...
Was going to be a very difficult task .
Sir ...
This Ifrit ...
What does it look like ?
You can 't see Ifrit .
You can only hear it breathe .
One can only see the Kalapori ( Black witch ) which follows it .
She is the one who delivers all it 's messages .
Ifrit is invisible to us .
Rukhsana !
Rukhsana ...
Are you inside ?
What happened to you ?
Why didn 't you eat your lunch ?
I wasn 't hungry .
You haven 't eaten all day . What do you mean you were not hungry ?
Come , let us eat together . Here ...
Take this , it is for you .
Yes , for you .
Come .
Should I change the channel ?
Do you want to watch a Bengali channel ?
Do you understand this ?
Let me see this .
Have you ever seen a television before ?
Oh , yes .
I have found a welfare home for you .
I 've been told it 's very nice .
Tomorrow , when I leave for work , I 'll drop you there .
Eat this .
I won 't go .
It is a nice place .
No ! What if he comes there as well ?
Nobody will follow you there . You will be safe .
They have televisions there as well .
I won 't go .
Rukhsana !
Rukhsana .
Rukhsana , please try to understand .
I cannot keep you here with me . If my parents find out ...
They won 't find out . I will be absolutely quiet ...
just like a mouse . Mother has taught me how .
They won 't find out . Nobody will know .
Okay , you don 't have to leave right now .
Please come out and eat your food .
What are you doing ?
I was hungry .
Why are you eating from the garbage bin ?
Are you crazy ?
There is food in the refrigerator .
Do you want some more ?
Is it enough ?
Tell me if you want more .
This is all there is .
Is it enough ?
It is bad .
What ?
Mother used to cough a lot .
I know it is bad .
Does this bother you ?
Never know , with you ...
You find incense sticks foul smelling .
It scares me .
Incense sticks ?
Really ?
Let me teach you something .
This will help you .
Press one side of your nose with your finger , like this .
And take a deep breath from the other side .
Then press the second side and breathe out from the first one .
Come on , try it .
Yes .
Don 't press both sides together . Yes ...
Get up ! Get up !
- I haven 't done anything . - Haven 't done anything ?
You 've been a prostitute for three years .
Now you pretend to be innocent ? Do you take me for a fool ?
" I 'm trying to find a mention of you In my silence "
" I speak not but how voluble is my silence "
" Why should these burning words Turn to frost on my lips "
" You are the answer to the questions raised by my silence If only you would listen . "
" I 'm trying to find a mention of you In my silence . "
" I speak not but how voluble is my silence . "
" My heart a moth , flies I know not where While your flame gently burns by its side . "
" It is time to set the weight of dreams lightly on the pillow "
" And follow the trail that will lead you to my heart . "
" I 'm trying to find a mention of you In my silence . "
" I speak not but how voluble is my silence . "
Here , please have some sweets .
Babai , take some for Piyali .
Are these yours ?
Yes . Mother has kept them carefully .
Thank you .
They 're still in good condition .
Didn 't your friends break any of these ?
No , I have never had this problem .
I 've never had friends .
What do you mean you 've never had friends ?
I mean , I didn 't have any .
I didn 't speak to other people .
I spoke so rarely that mother was afraid that I 'd lose my voice .
And when there were guests at home ...
You would hide under the bed , wouldn 't you ?
Your mother told me this .
Yes .
I would refuse to come out , no matter how hard they tried .
Rukhsana ?
Rukhsana ? What is wrong ?
Go away ! Leave me alone !
- I 'll get a doctor . - No , you won 't .
Rukhsana !
Rukhsana ! Don 't be childish , come outside .
I will be alright .
Leave me alone now .
Rukhsana , please let me help you .
You won 't be able to do anything .
This happens to me sometimes .
Once a month ...
Oh !
Mr. Aalam has sent us .
Uncle , please save me .
They have tied me to this spot .
They hit me ...
Abuse me .
They say I am some Kalapori .
Please help me , uncle .
Get me out of here .
Save me , uncle .
Help me ...
What do you want ?
You bastard !
Where did you find this ?
Do you want to know where she is ?
Why should I tell you ?
I want something in return .
What are you willing to give ?
Hey ...
Will you give me a child ?
Tell me , old man .
Will you ...
make me pregnant ?
Tell me ...
since you have such fire within you ...
why don 't you give me some ?
Give me a child .
You , old man ... Will you give me a child ?
Give me ... give me a child . Give ...
Ready to talk ?
Don 't you dare lie to me .
Else , you won 't even get a place in hell , after I 'm done with you .
A flower ...
She has blossomed .
She has put oil in her hair today .
Where is she ?
I don 't know .
But she is happy .
She has just spewed out the poison .
She is calm now .
What is it ?
There is a boy with her now .
A boy ? Who ?
I don 't know .
You don 't know or do you not want to tell me ?
He is young .
I am sure he loves her as well .
It is accomplished .
Soon she will accomplish what she was born to do .
She won 't be able to .
Faris ...
Hey old man ...
She will devour ...
All of you , one by one .
Spread the blood ...
Spread the bloodline ...
Are you alright ?
Hmm .
You scared me last night .
What are you sketching ?
Hello .
Good morning .
So , what time did you get back last night ?
Around eleven-thirty .
- Did you manage to get a train at night ? - Yes , I got a train .
The last ... no , the second last one .
In the rain ?
Yes , it was raining very heavily .
I hope you didn 't get wet .
Hello ? What happened ?
No , nothing .
You know what , a lot of people are falling sick now .
You might fall ill if you get wet .
You live alone .
This is happening often nowadays .
In Salt Lake , thieves broke into a house after poisoning their dog .
Mrs. Pakrashi ...
What is that mark on the neck ?
Dabru knew ...
He was about to die .
He was not eating properly last two days .
Don 't worry , you go out . I will manage .
Spread the blood ...
Spread the bloodline ...
Let me go ! Leave me ! Let me go !
Spread the blood ... Spread the bloodline ...
No ... no ... no .
What have you done ?
I searched ... but I couldn 't find it .
The nail cutter . I couldn 't find it .
So you used a knife ?
Are you mad ?
It will heal .
Shut up ! What will I tell everybody , if something happens to you ?
Nothing will happen to me . Nothing happens to me .
Oh ... take this .
Forgive me .
I should be the one asking for forgiveness .
I am really sorry .
Why did you throw away my cigarettes ?
Because you threw them away ... I hid this , just for fun .
I didn 't throw them away .
You didn 't throw them away ?
So you didn 't ?
You didn 't ?
Do you want some tea ?
Yes .
- Hello ! - Yes ? I 'll call you back ?
- Okay . - Yeah .
She keeps calling you .
Who ?
That girl ...
Who was asking you the other day ...
' What time did you return home ? '
I ...
I don 't like her .
Don 't speak to her .
Hello , Mr. Arnab .
Do you know a girl named Rukhsana ?
Who ? Who is Rukhsana ?
Hey , didn 't you come with that girl to the morgue the other day ?
Want me to remind you ? You liar !
Her mother is the one who had an accident with your car .
- Oh , okay , that girl ? - Yes that girl .
Yes , but why are you asking me all this ?
Why ?
Isn 't she living with you nowadays ?
What nonsense is this !
Why will she live with me ?
Her mother died in that accident .
You probably feel responsible for her now .
It was a case of suicide . Everybody knows that .
Are you accusing me ?
No .
I 'm just trying to tell you something .
That girl does not deserve your sympathy .
She is not a human .
What ?
She is a fairy .
Not the kind you read about in children 's fairytales .
She is the daughter of Ifrit .
Conceived during the time of Oladhchakra , She is very dangerous .
We 've been searching for her for a long time . - Are you mad ?
Who are you people ?
Who let you in ? Security ! Security !
Mr. Arnab , you misunderstand my words .
That fairy is not as helpless and delicate as she seems .
She will make you fall in love with her .
And you will get trapped in her web of lies .
What is this ?
How did you let these people in ?
- Get them out of here . - Come on ! Let 's go !
Mr. Arnab , she 's the one who has kept you close to her ...
- And not the other way around . - Please leave !
Where ? Huh ?
Because she needs you for something .
The day she gets it , she will lovingly devour you .
I see ... she already has .
Following me , huh ?
- What ... what do you want ? - What the hell is your problem ?
Should I call the police ?
- Will I call the police ? - You want to call the police ?
What happened to you ?
Why are those men searching for you ?
What do they want ?
Who did this to you ?
Those men ... I have no idea what they were talking about .
About ... some ...
Oladhchakra , Ifrit ... some fairy ...
What on earth are all these ?
Is this some kind of a trap ?
Who did this to you ?
Are you trying to set me up ?
That bloody man from the morgue .
I fought back ...
Forget about it .
Now tell me ...
Are you setting up a trap ?
Sir ... please listen to me .
He caught hold of me .
Yes ! I surreptitiously followed him .
I swear !
Sir , I don 't know how that bugger found out !
H ... hello ?
Hello ?
Hey Prahlaad !
Prahlaad !
Prahlaad ! You scoundrel ! Who did this ?
What happened ?
How are you feeling ?
Much better .
I 've been trying to call you .
I 'm so sorry , it was very late by the time I got back last night
I 've been trying from last night ...
But your phone ...
Where are you now ? Are you at home ?
- Yes , I am . - Someone is coming .
One minute ... just hold .
- What ? - There 's someone there .
- No , there isn 't . - There is . - No .
Hello ...
Yes , I 'll just be there .
Come with me .
- Why is she here ? - Please ... just listen to me . Please ...
- Please stay inside . - Why ?
No matter what , don 't come out of the room .
Please ...
Coming !
I thought you wouldn 't open ... What happened to you ?
Nothing , just a small accident .
You had an accident and you didn 't tell me about it !
- Did you go to a doctor ? - Yes .
Let me see .
Which doctor did you visit ?
He didn 't even bandage the wound .
Do you have some bandage at home ?
No , just let it be . It 's fine now .
Okay , I 'll get the bandage .
You ... you come with me .
Sit down . Here , in this room .
I 'll get it .
By the way ...
I was so upset with you yesterday .
I had to tell you something very important .
I tried to call you so many times !
But you didn 't receive my calls .
Hey !
This room is nice .
Did you sketch these ?
Yes .
Oh wow !
You didn 't tell me that you 're an artist as well .
Will you make a sketch ? Of me .
Sit here . Come , give this to me .
It 's done .
Okay .
Are you scared ?
No ...
Want to try yoga ?
- You ... - Dear one .
Me ?
When you love someone , you address them like this .
- Oh ... I am sorry , I didn 't mean to ... - No , I am sorry . I shouldn 't have ...
No , actually ...
How did you get up there ?
Call me dear one .
What ?
- Rukh ... Rukhsana ... wait ... - Shh ...
Piyali ...
Piyali ? Just listen to me ! Piyali , please .
I thought you were an honest guy .
That is why I had agreed ...
I didn 't want to hide anything from you .
I had come here to tell you something .
But you are the one hiding things from me .
- I feel like such a fool ! - Piyali , that 's not true . Please ...
What were you thinking ?
Just because of one mistake , You think you can do whatever you want ?
There is nothing between us , okay ?
Come on , leave ... just leave !
If you don 't , I 'll throw you out .
I won 't leave !
Forgive me .
Please , forgive me .
Please ...
Forgive me .
What do you think ?
She didn 't spew much poison .
It wasn 't for keeping herself alive , Faris .
Just enough to kill him .
Kalapori was wrong .
It is not the boy ...
it is the girl who has fallen in love .
Can I take these ?
Where will you go ?
The people from that welfare home have asked you to go on Monday .
' Another incident that shows the rising crime rate in our city . '
' Last night at Katapukur Morgue , the body of an employee was discovered . '
' Name of the employee was Kanai Sahoo . '
' With us is another employee , who claims to have seen a girl ... '
' Let us talk to him . '
- Hello ? - I 'm calling off this wedding .
Please don 't keep calling me .
' In 1990 , certain reports from the Satkhira district of Bangladesh ...
' had spread fear among the people . '
' Several minor girls were reported to be missing ... '
' from the areas around Satkhira district . '
' It is believed that a satanic group called Oladhchakra was behind these abductions . '
' The objective of this group was to continue the lineage of Ifrit . '
Spread the blood ...
Spread the bloodline ...
' When the news of this demonic monster spread ... '
' It gave rise to a movement against the Oladhchakra ... '
' Doomsday Movement . '
' This movement was led by Qasim Ali , a professor at Dhaka University . '
' The public was supportive of this movement ... '
' But due to their extremist methods and actions ... '
' The government declared the group illegal and banned them . '
' Ifrit is the most dangerous Djinn . '
' You can 't see Ifrit . '
' You can only hear it breathe . '
' Ifrit is capable of having sexual relations with human beings . '
' As a result of which , women can give birth to its child . '
' These children are born within a month of the lunar calendar ... '
' Instead of the usual nine months . '
' They are born without an umbilical cord or a navel . '
' Poison runs in the veins of these children ... '
' And if they don 't get rid of the poison once a month , they die . '
' The sole purpose of these beings is to give birth to more such children ... '
' And continue this demonic line . '
Spread the blood ...
Spread the bloodline ...
Where were you ?
What happened ?
She ... she was back !
She is calling me .
Please don 't leave me and go .
I am so scared .
If you want to stay here with me , then ...
Can you feel it ?
Feel what ?
I am pregnant .
I can hear someone coming .
Go , the door is open .
Yes .
Why are you still sitting here ? Shut the door .
Arnab !
Arnab , someone is coming . Go .
Arnab ...
Arnab ! Don 't go away !
Arnab !
He ... will kill me !
He will kill me . Don 't go .
Save me !
He will kill our child , Arnab !
How long ... ?
It will take time .
It takes time to kill them .
We will inform you .
Done ?
That 's it ... enough .
Look what they have done to you !
Just see ... what these idiots have done !
Wait , don 't move .
Rukhsana ...
So , we finally meet ...
Even if it 's for the last time .
Oh , Babai ! Piyali 's father had called us .
- What happened between the two of you ? - What happened ?
Hey ! Babai !
Babai , tell us what hapened at least .
What happened Babai ?
What is this boy doing ?
Keep on hitting her .
As she gets more and more angry ...
The poison in her will increase .
We will kill her with her own poison .
What ?
It took us so long to find this last one .
Let her suffer before she dies .
She deserves it .
Babai , my child !
See who is here . Open the door ...
Strange , she has been knocking on the door for so long and you ...
Babai !
Why are you doing all this ?
You haven 't left the room in three weeks .
Everyone is blaming me !
What else could I have done , after what happened ?
Go outside right now and tell everybody the truth !
- If you don 't , then I ... - Truth ?
About that girl .
- Then maybe ... - She isn 't just a girl .
She is a monster .
Ifrit 's daughter .
How much longer will it take ?
Not long now .
Just a few hours more .
All I know is that ...
She is carrying my child .
And I left her all alone ...
to die .
So who is the monster here ?
Is it her or me ?
Arnab ...
there is a monster in all of us .
Do you remember ?
I wanted to tell you something the other day ...
about my affair with that man .
The doctor with the bike ?
Our affair didn 't end just like that .
I was pregnant .
At first ...
everything was alright .
Suddenly , he called me up one day and said ...
he couldn 't carry on .
That 's all he said .
So ... I ...
had to do it by myself .
It had already been three months .
I had even heard the heartbeat during sonography .
Every time I put my hand on my stomach ...
I could feel it .
I still do .
Yes , tell me . Piyali , where are you ?
I just ... reached home . Just hold for a minute .
Hello ! Hello Piyali ?
Sorry , the key had got stuck .
Close all the doors and windows of the house .
Why ? What happened ?
She is still alive . She will come for you .
- What ? How do you ... ? - Listen to me .
Don 't open the door ... for anybody , till I come there .
Open your mouth and take a deep breath .
Like this , a deep breath .
Keep breathing ...
I can see the head . Push ... push harder .
Push ... push harder .
Push harder .
Piyali ...
Are you alright ? Why didn 't you answer my call ?
She is gone .
Who ?
Rukhsana ...
She left the child with me and went away .
Child ?
After the delivery , I went in to get some towels ...
She had left by the time I returned .
I wonder where she has gone .
Why have you come here ?
Go away !
Go away from here !
Do you hear me ?
Don 't come near me !
They understand everything .
They know when I have to spew out the poison .
But they never desert me .
Please forgive me , Rukhsana .
I was scared .
But with my child ...
You don 't need to be scared .
He is not like me .
Don 't be afraid of him .
That child was born with a navel and an umbilical cord .
This was probably because his birth was ...
not the outcome of Ifrit 's malevolence ...
but Rukhsana 's love .
Rukhsana had made a sudden appearance in my life ...
and one fine day , she disappeared .
She probably went back to the place ...
where all fairies return to ...
after the story ends .